<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adp</title>
    <link>https://adpblg.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on adp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adpblg.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>p4ssw0rd$</title>
      <link>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/passwords/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of password advice out there. Some if it is good, and some of it is really bad. This post is a quick dive into passwords; there&amp;rsquo;s theory, practice, and even a bit of hacking. By the end you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to give out your own, high quality, password advice.
 password_theory_123 password space Passwords exist in two dimensions, which we shall refer to as length and depth. A password is constructed from one or more elements, or symbols for the purpose of this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mapping music</title>
      <link>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/mapping-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/mapping-music/</guid>
      <description>I was going a bit mad during lockdown, and this was one of the small projects that kept me going.
It also helped get me a job!
 mapping music  During lockdown, like you, I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to a lot of music. I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to so much music that I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself thinking about how to think about the ways I listen to music.
oh man you&amp;rsquo;re gonna love this next track At parties, when we used to have parties, I remember finding myself listening to a song and immediately thinking about what song I wanted to listen to next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>internet explorer</title>
      <link>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/internet-explorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/internet-explorer/</guid>
      <description>This blog post is an exploration into the wiring of the internet. When we move information across the internet, what does its path look like?
 to boldly go where many have gone before addressing the internet When I was fifteen I had (or I thought I had) this real funny desktop background,
Now, years later, I have a better background and a computer science degree. But it turns out that the internet is not so different from the postal system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>counting change</title>
      <link>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/counting-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adpblg.co.uk/post/counting-change/</guid>
      <description>Introduction about this piece. Ultimately I wrote it because I was bored, which is not a great intro is it?
 hello world When I first began my formal study of computer science at high school, my teacher asked me to write a program that would dispense change from a self-service machine.
The rules were simple. My machine would only have 10p, 5p, 2p, and 1p coins. When it was time to dispense change, my program would take as input the amount in pennies and dispense the minimum number of coins required to make the correct change.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>